https://www.wiego.org/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy covers WIEGO’s entire website, www.wiego.org. It does not apply to pages hosted by other organizations, including those to which WIEGO’s website might link.
Our website may be used without entering any personal information.
Certain services and features listed below, however, do potentially use personally identifiable information either at your direct request, such as when you join a mailing list, or when you make a comment on our website.
We Respect Your Privacy
WIEGO will always protect your information, and never use any personal information collected from this website for purposes other than those for which you have given express and specific consent.
We will never sell or provide your information to other organizations without your permission.
We will only send you material (such as newsletters) that you have requested, and you can unsubscribe at any time.
Cookies
We use cookies, which are small amounts of data stored on your computer and used to track certain parts of your interaction with our website, to customize and improve your experience. Cookies are also set and accessed by third-party data processors, including Google Analytics. While this records information such as geographical location, device type, internet browser and operating system, none of this data personally identifies you. It does, however, allow us to analyze usage patterns to determine what information our visitors need, and lets us provide the best possible experience.
Newsletters
Our website contains links to subscription forms that allow you to sign up for news and newsletters from the WIEGO Network. We use a third-party data processor, MailChimp, to manage our mailings. Please see their legal and privacy policies and practices here.
If you choose to subscribe to a WIEGO newsletter or newsfeed, we require a valid email address, first and last name, and your preferred language. You may choose to provide other information (such as your location and professional affiliation) but it is not required.
This information is retained by both WIEGO and the external mailing service and will remain within WIEGO’s and the third party’s databases for as long as we continue to use those services for email marketing, or until you request to be removed from the newsletter. You may cancel your subscription at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe” link contained in every email newsletter we send.
Social Networks
WIEGO uses social networking platform, and our website contains links to these networks and our profiles on them. These third-party companies process your personal information, and maintain their own privacy policies, which are available for your review here:
Facebook
LinkedIn
Twitter
YouTube
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
This privacy policy may change from time to time in line with legislation or industry developments. Any changes we make will be posted on this page, and specific policy changes and updates will be mentioned in the change log below.
Questions or Concerns? Please contact us.
Plaidoyer pour un travail décent : Les récupératrice·eur·s de matériaux en Amérique latine documentent des violations des droits humainsBy
Federico Parra, Tania Espinosa Sánchez
Human rights violations signal urgent need to improve waste pickers’ working conditions in Latin AmericaBy
Tania Espinosa Sánchez, Federico Parra
Violaciones a los derechos humanos de
recicladores en Latinoamérica señalan urgencia de mejorar sus condiciones de trabajoBy
Federico Parra, Tania Espinosa Sánchez
Trabajadoras y trabajadores en empleo informal ven un largo camino hacia la recuperación, a menos que los gobiernos actúenBy
Sally Roever, Michael Rogan
Informal Workers See a Long Road to Recovery Ahead — Unless Governments ActBy
Home-based workers in Bulgaria: Using the ILO Reporting Mechanism to Work
Not just hunger but also safety: Relief for waste pickers during COVID-19
Impact of COVID-19 on Street Vendors in India: Status and Steps for Advocacy
Informal Economy Monitoring Study (IEMS)
Informal Economy Budget Analysis (IEBA)
Blogs
